No luggage. Just baggage.
Kangaroo Island is a drama, comedy film directed by Timothy David.
Lou Wells has hit rock bottom after a promising start to her Hollywood career.
Now broke and aimless, she reluctantly accepts a plane ticket from her estranged father,
Rory to return home to South Australia’s ruggedly beautiful Kangaroo Island.
As years of unresolved tension start to resurface, the reunion turns even more
complicated when Lou and her sister Freya learn about Rory’s secret.
Lou Wells, played by Rebecca Breeds.
Rory Wells, played by Erik Thomson.
Freya Wells, played by Adelaide Clemens.
Ben Roberts, played by Joel Jackson.
Todd, played by Louis Henbest.
Auntie Rose, played by Julie Wood.
Kangaroo Island is a 2024 Australian drama/comedy film directed
by Timothy David and written by Sally Gifford.
Its name derives from Kangaroo Island in South Australia, where it was filmed.
Its world premiere was at the Adelaide Film Festival on 3 November 2024, and it
is scheduled for release in Australian cinemas on 21 August 2025.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.